<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>CommandPost Changelog</title>
		<link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CommandPost/CommandPost/develop/appcast/appcast.xml</link>
		<description>Most recent changes with links to updates.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<item>
			<title>Version 1.1.5</title>
			<description><![CDATA[
				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.5</h1>

				<h2>New Features:</h2>
				<ul><li>If you assign an action to a Loupedeck CT/Live Touchscreen button that has an image in the Search Console, that image will now be automatically applied to the button. For example, if you apply the action to launch Disk Utility to a Loupedeck CT/Live Touchscreen Button, the Disk Utility icon will be automatically applied. Thanks for suggesting Eric Badura!</li>
				<li>You can now select Applications (in addition to image files) when you click the Image Drop Zone in the Loupedeck CT/Live Control Surfaces panel.</li></ul>

				<h2>Known Issues:</h2>
				<ul><li>Due to a suspected bug in Xcode 12, the Search Console results in Mojave &amp; Catalina no longer display the full width of the Search Console window, but it looks correct in Big Sur. We've contacted Apple to try and come up with a fix.</li></ul>

				<hr />

				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.4</h1>

				<h2>Changes:</h2>
				<ul><li>On a fresh installation, CommandPost will no longer ask you if you want to copy the CommandPost application to your application folder. Instead, you should manually copy CommandPost to the application folder via the Applications shortcut in the DMG package. This has been changed to get around issues where people want to install CommandPost in their user-specific application folder, or when there's permission issues trying to copy CommandPost across, which can happen on some Big Sur installations.</li></ul>

				<h2>Bug Fixes:</h2>
				<ul><li>Fixed the "Zoom to selection" action in Final Cut Pro. Thanks for reporting Jeffrey Linneman!</li>
				<li>Fixed the "Save Current Frame" option in the Final Cut Pro Viewer Overlay popup. Thanks for reporting David Brown!</li></ul>

				<hr />

				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.3</h1>

				<h2>New Features:</h2>
				<ul><li>Added actions that adjust the Position controls in Final Cut Pro's inspector in reverse using MIDI. Thanks Joe Dull!</li>
				<li>Added an action to "Toggle Opacity Fade Handles in Video Animation Popup on Selected Clips". Thanks for the suggestion Ripple Training! Unfortunately, due to a bug in Final Cut Pro's Accessibility API this doesn't work for clips within a secondary storyline container.</li>
				<li>Added preferences to change the Search Console width and height. This can be found when you right click on the Search Console. Each individual Search Console has its own unique width and height (i.e. the Search Console in Final Cut Pro can be different than in After Effects).</li></ul>

				<h2>Improvements:</h2>
				<ul><li>DaVinci Resolve & After Effects Tangent support is now disabled by default on a fresh install.</li>
				<li>Updated the Shot Data Motion Template, so that it works with all common aspect ratios. Thanks Iain Anderson!</li>
				<li>We've removed the EULA from the CommandPost DMG, and updated the tag-line to match the website.</li>
				<li>We've adjusted the window sizes on Big Sur so there's not as much wasted space at the bottom of the windows.</li>
				<li>The Shared Pasteboard will no longer prompt you on CommandPost's startup if the shared folder is not accessible. This means that if you're using something like PostLab Drive, the Shared Pasteboard will now work when the drive is connected, and you won't get notified if the drive becomes disconnected. Thanks for reporting Dale Ryan Leckie!</li></ul>

				<h2>Bug Fixes:</h2>
				<ul><li>Fixed a bug where the menu bar actions had the wrong menu path in the Search Console subtext.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where you will be asked for Accessibility Permissions straight away on a fresh install. Thanks for reporting Iain Anderson!</li></ul>

				<hr />

				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.2</h1>

				<h2>Bug Fixes:</h2>
				<ul><li>Fixed a bug that could cause the hue control in the Final Cut Pro Colour Wheels to change its value to 90 degrees when CommandPost first loads, if the Colour Wheel is active on a clip. Thanks for reporting Valerio D'Andrassi.</li></ul>

				<h2>Improvements:</h2>
				<ul><li>The Shot Data Motion Template has been updated. Thanks Vigneswaran Rajkumar!</li></ul>

				<hr />

				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.1</h1>

				<h2>Improvements:</h2>
				<ul><li>We've added some caching to dramatically increase the responsiveness of control surfaces, such as the Loupedeck CT. This has massive improvements for controlling the Color Wheels with the Loupedeck CT Touch Screen, for example.</li></ul>

				<h2>New Actions:</h2>
				<ul><li>We've added new actions to control the Final Cut Pro Color Board, by increments of 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 and 10. They are all contained within their own Action Group called "Color Board" on the Search Console. Thanks for suggesting Eric Badura!</li></ul>

				<h2>Bug Fixes:</h2>
				<ul><li>Fixed the Hue controls on Tangent Panels. Thanks for reporting Robert J. Bradshaw!</li>
				<li>Fixed an error that could occur randomly when refreshing Loupedeck devices. Thanks for reporting Eric Badura!</li>
				<li>Some actions that used popup menus (such as "Show Horizon") weren't working correctly. This is now fixed. Thanks for reporting Adam Terlanda!</li>
				<li>Some fields weren't being correctly exported in the Shot Data Toolbox Utility. This is now fixed. Thanks for reporting Vigneswaran Rajkumar!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug which cause a MIDI error when launching CommandPost 1.1 or later for the first time. Thanks for reporting Scott Dodson!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where Stream Deck settings weren't migrated from CommandPost 1.0.6 (or earlier) to 1.1 (or later). The Final Cut Pro and All Applications settings are now automatically migrated to the Stream Deck Unit 1.</li></ul>

				<hr />

				<h1>CommandPost 1.1.0</h1>

				<h2>Control Surfaces Support:</h2>
				<ul><li>Control Surfaces have been moved out of Preferences into their own window.</li>
				<li>Added Loupedeck (original), Loupedeck CT and Loupedeck Live support.</li>
				<li>Added Stream Deak XL and Stream Deck Mini support.</li>
				<li>Added TourBox support.</li>
				<li>Added placeholder Control Surface panels for Monogram and Gamepad, with an explanation of how to use these control surfaces with CommandPost until we add built-in support.</li>
				<li>MIDI, Loupedeck &amp; Stream Deck Preferences panels now support Custom Applications.</li>
				<li>AudioSwift now correctly works with CommandPost&#39;s MIDI functionality. Thanks for reporting Nigel Rios!</li>
				<li>Added Skype, Microsoft Teams, Zoom, Disk Utility, System Preferences and TextEdit to the default Control Surfaces application drop-down lists. However, currently there is only basic keyboard shortcut actions for Skype.</li>
				<li>Tangent panel support has been re-engineered to support multiple CommandPost applications within Tangent Mapper (i.e. you can now have a completely seperate Tangent Mapper layout for Final Cut Pro and DaVinci Resolve). Better support for DaVinci Resolve will come in a future beta - this release it just laying the foundations.</li></ul>

				<h2>Toolbox Utilities:</h2>
				<ul><li>The FCPXML Titles Processor allows you update the titles within a FCPXML, based on new data from a CSV file. This utility was commissioned by Connor Eberhart.</li>
				<li>Shot Data is new specialised Toolbox utility that allows you to import a FCPXML which contains one or more Shot Data Titles in a timeline, and converts the data from these Motion Templates into a single CSV file for use in other applications. This feature has been commissioned by Vigneswaran Rajkumar for his upcoming feature film.</li></ul>

				<h2>New Features:</h2>
				<ul><li>Added non-keyboard shortcut actions for Final Cut Pro Browser Clip Height &amp; Browser Duration.</li>
				<li>Added speed rate actions for 40, 50, and 200.</li>
				<li>Added actions to increase and decrease display brightness.</li>
				<li>Added actions for adjusting opacity in Final Cut Pro.</li>
				<li>Added actions for Filmstrip &amp; List Mode in the Final Cut Pro Browser.</li>
				<li>Added a Contrast action for Final Cut Pro which adjusts shadows &amp; highlights brightness at the same time.</li>
				<li>Added actions for Timeline Zoom (using the Appearance Popup). Thanks for suggesting Prescott Van Leer!</li>
				<li>All your Keyboard Maestro Macros are now available in the Search Console as actions.</li>
				<li>Added initial support for Adobe After Effects. There are now actions for each individual effect in After Effects, as well as actions for all the shortcut keys and menubar items.</li>
				<li>Added actions for Zoom keyboard shortcuts. Thanks for your assistance Jonathan Zuck!</li>
				<li>CommandPost can now generate menu bar actions for all Custom Applications.</li>
				<li>Added an option to create Captions when using the Text To Speech feature in Final Cut Pro. Thanks for the suggestion Vigneswaran Rajkumar!</li>
				<li>Added actions that allow you to &quot;emulate&quot; a Tangent Element panel in DaVinci Resolve. This feature requires Tangent support to be enabled, and at least one physical Tangent device to be connected to your machine (i.e. a Tangent Ripple). This means you can now use Tangent Mapper to customise your DaVinci Resolve layout for any Tangent panel, as well as trigger Tangent actions from any other control surface or shortcut key (i.e. you can control a colour wheel from a Loupedeck CT or TourBox). It also means you can control DaVinci Resolve from a Tangent Arc or CP200.</li>
				<li>Added a Contrast Color Wheel control to Tangent Mapper. Thanks for suggesting Von Jackson!</li></ul>

				<h2>Improvements:</h2>
				<ul><li>Recompiled CommandPost to natively support Apple Silicon.</li>
				<li>Improved the method we detect &quot;Screen Recording&quot; permissions on macOS Catalina &amp; Big Sur.</li>
				<li>We now use Sentry instead of Firebase Crashlytics for tracking crashes.</li>
				<li>CommandPost now uses Lua 5.4.</li>
				<li>We&#39;ve made lots of changes and improvements to our underlying Final Cut Pro X API. These changes should make writing your own Lua Snippets a lot more simple and easy to understand.</li>
				<li>The Search Console now loads faster, and displays a &quot;loading&quot; message when the contents of the Search Console is still populating. We&#39;ve also adjusted the way the Search Console orders its results to improve usability.</li>
				<li>Added more Touch Bar icons. Thanks Daniele Di Tuccio!</li>
				<li>Changed the way we trigger shortcut keys for better performance.</li>
				<li>HUD now watches for Viewer resizing.</li>
				<li>Browser Playhead Highlight now follows playhead when visible.</li>
				<li>&quot;Select Clips Forward/Backwards&quot; actions now selects clips with speed handles.</li>
				<li>Timeline Batch Export now correctly handles clips with speed handles visible.</li>
				<li>Removed unnecessary &quot;Failed to cache User Effects Presets” debug message in Plugin Scanner.</li>
				<li>Added option to enable/disable all draggable guides in Final Cut Pro Viewer Overlay.</li>
				<li>Improved the performance of the Video Inspector actions.</li>
				<li>Improved the MIDI Controls for Colour Wheels, so that you can use both the horizontal and vertical actions at the same time. This allows you to use the controls smoothly in AudioSwift using X/Y mode. Thanks for reporting Nigel Rios!</li>
				<li>Added relative MIDI actions for controlling the Final Cut Pro Colour Board. Thanks Nigel Rios!</li>
				<li>We now just play an error sound instead of showing a dialog box when a menubar action cannot be triggered. Thanks Knut Hake!</li>
				<li>You can now use a velocity value for the &quot;Note Off&quot; and &quot;Note On&quot; MIDI commands. The velocity is also now detected and filled out in the MIDI Preferences panel when you use the &quot;Learn&quot; button. Thanks Nigel Rios!</li>
				<li>Improved the &quot;Relative A&quot; MIDI Controls for the Color Board &amp; Color Wheels, for use with AudioSwift (and other MIDI devices).</li>
				<li>&quot;Sections&quot; in the Search Console has been renamed to &quot;Show Action Groups&quot;, and is now grouped by application.</li>
				<li>The &quot;Text to Speech&quot; feature has been re-designed and improved.</li>
				<li>Actions that trigger virtual keyboard presses now take into account any modifier keys triggered by the &quot;Press and hold Modifier Key&quot; actions. Thanks for reporting Flavio Saramin!</li></ul>

				<h2>Bug Fixes:</h2>
				<ul><li>Fixed Touch Bar support on 16-inch MacBook Pro.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug in Search Console where toggling “Search Subtext” wouldn’t take affect until the Search Console was closed and re-opened.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug where the Effects &amp; Transitions search box contents would not be restored correctly after applying an effect or transition via an action.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug in Notes HUD panel.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug in Final Cut Pro Crop Bottom Action.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug where double quotation marks in Snippet names prevented the Snippets from being editable.</li>
				<li>Fixed bug which prevented the &quot;Clear&quot; buttons in the Loupedeck+ preferences panel from working.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug in the &quot;Press and hold&quot; modifier actions for CONTROL, OPTION and COMMAND. Thanks for reporting Knut Hake!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where the &quot;Make Pasteboard Text Uppercase/Lowercase/Camelcase&quot; actions would not affect certain characters such as &quot;å&quot;. Thanks for reporting Eivind Lie Nitter!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where the Search Console was incorrectly case sensitive.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug which prevented the individual &quot;Play&quot; and &quot;Pause&quot; actions from functioning. A better description for these actions has also been added to the Search Console, so that it&#39;s clearer to understand their purpose (i.e. the play button only plays - it won&#39;t stop playback). Thanks for reporting Prescott Van Leer!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where Colour Wheel actions wouldn&#39;t not automatically change to the Colour Wheel Inspector if you were on the Colour Curves. Thanks for reporting Prescott Van Leer!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug in the Timeline Batch Export tool, where sometimes CommandPost could fail to change the destination directory.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug which prevented MIDI commands from applying correctly if you manually entered them in the MIDI Preferences panel (as opposed to using the &quot;Learn&quot; button). Thanks Nigel Rios!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug in the Text to Speech function and Media Watch Folders where certain non-alphanumeric characters in filenames could cause the functions to fail. Thanks for reporting Vigneswaran Rajkumar!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug which prevented Color Wheels from opening correctly in the Final Cut Pro Inspector when you moved a Tangent wheel or knob.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug in MIDI Timeline Scroll action.</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where the &quot;Leave Files in Place&quot; menubar item tick was incorrectly reversed. Thanks for reporting Mark Westcott!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug that could cause certain items to not appear in the Search Console, due to a &quot;Share Destinations&quot; folder not existing on some machines. Thanks for reporting Peter Moss!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug with the Jog/Shuttle control for Tangent Panels in Final Cut Pro. Thanks for reporting Vigneswaran Rajkumar!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug where a deleted Media Watch Folder would reappear when you restarted CommandPost. Thanks for reporting Erik Lathouwers, Matt Steeves &amp; Jiří Fiala!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug which prevented Color Board controls from working in some newer versions of Final Cut Pro when the interface was in German. Thanks for reporting Eric Badura!</li>
				<li>Fixed a bug that would cause an error if you tried to Restore a Browser Layout that wasn&#39;t previously saved. Thanks for reporting Gábor Kertai!</li></ul>
			]]>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 22:52:55 +1100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://github.com/CommandPost/CommandPost/releases/download/1.1.5/CommandPost_1.1.5.dmg"
				sparkle:version="6565"
                sparkle:shortVersionString="1.1.5"
				sparkle:dsaSignature="MC0CFG9Qk2Td91S5ucbVBGmhcZkRUpRtAhUA7+Uhr2G7SUMNT79PIkG+XxwSn0I="
				type="application/octet-stream"
			/>
			<sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>10.12</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>